{
    "subject": "resource/Mark_Miloscia",
    "predicate": "property/birthDate",
    "object": "1958-09-13",
    "human_readable": "Mark Miloscia was born on September 13, 1958.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9588216543197632,
            "question": "September 13th of which year marks Mark Miloscia's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.948513388633728,
            "question": "Could someone born on September 13th be named Mark Miloscia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8971627354621887,
            "question": "When was Mark Miloscia born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7966829538345337,
            "question": "What is the significance of September 13th for Mark Miloscia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.796380877494812,
            "question": "Is Mark Miloscia a September baby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7847884297370911,
            "question": "What is Mark Miloscia's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6247109770774841,
            "question": "What month and day was Mark Miloscia born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5563187599182129,
            "question": "When did Mark Miloscia celebrate his birth anniversary last?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.47576814889907837,
            "question": "In what year did Mark Miloscia come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3557436168193817,
            "question": "If today is October 1st, has it already passed Mark Miloscia's birthday this year?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mark Miloscia was born on September 13, 1958.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6486_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Mark Miloscia come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6486_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Mark Miloscia celebrate his birth anniversary last?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6486_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What month and day was Mark Miloscia born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6486_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6486_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6486_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6486_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6486_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6486_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6486_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6486_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6486_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6486_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6486_66.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the requested format:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents provide information about Mark Anthony Miloscia, including his date of birth as \"September 13, 1958\", which matches the query."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}